Yaksh Thaker



Contact

Address:

B-606, Shantideep Flat, New Ranip, Ahmedabad-382480

Phone:

+91 9558981341

DOB:

08th November 1991

Marital Status:

Married

Email:

yakshthaker0811@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/yaksh-thaker-25510453

Hobbies

- Writing
- Sketching
- Photography
- Design

Strength

Positive Attitude Quick Thinking Work Ethic

Summary

Multi-tasking ability over one decad of experience in Pharmaceutical Machinery, Robotics Engineering & all type of Packaging Machine Manufacturing Division. I can manage consistency in customer support standers, manage people, and playing a mentorship role to key customer support personal by assisting them in the execution of duties. The ability to work well both as part of a team and on own as well.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Customer Support
- Technical Sales
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

PROJECT MANAGER URL Aseptic Automation Inc., Ahmedabad

MAY 2021 to Present

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Project/Service Executive Kevision System, Ahmedabad

NOV 2017 to MAY 2022

- Can manage consistency in customer support standards.
- Manage people and playing a mentorship role to key customer support personal by assisting them in the execution of duties.
- Ensuring constant sharpening their skills.
- Create a Service revenue by delivering service activities worldwide.

Sr. Service Engineer J-Pack Engineers Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

AUG 2014 to NOV 2017

 Improving Customer Service quality results by studying evaluating n redesigning processes; establishing and communicating service metrics, monitoring n analyzing results; implementing changes.

Languages

Gujarati – Native Hindi – Fluent English – Excellent

Quality Process Exposure

- Total Productive Maintenance for reliable productivity
- Kaizen 5S Framework
- 5S methodology

Software/Technology Exposure

Functional Software:

Solid-works

AutoCAD

Microsoft Office

MSSQL & MySQL(Start-up level of

Database)

Task management software:

ERP and SAP

Work Preference

Availability:

30 to 40 Days

Desired Job Type:

Full Time

Can Travel to Work:

Extensively

Current Location:

Ahmedabad

Willing to Relocate:

Yes

Residency/Visa:

Work Permit Require to work outside India

- Monitoring & Training Technicians for Machine Assembly.
- Managing both internal n external relationships on behalf of the customer support department.
- Ensuring service activities are seen to deliver measurable and significant value to the business.

Production Engineer Grid Bots Technology Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

MAR 2013 to AUG 2014

- Handle Planning, Purchase, Stores, & Quality Department.
- Manufacturing, testing, and dispatching automation Robots with proper documents to the customer.
 Reputed customer includes Bhabha Atomic Research Centre (BARC), ISRO, ONGC, and many more clients.
- Have handled various manufacturing Products like Robotic Arm, Delta Robot, AGV, SCARA Robots, etc.

Service Engineer

Hi-Tech Machinery Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

DEC 2012 to MAR 2013

- Basic troubleshooting, installation, maintenance and repair on designated equipment.
- Completing Preventative Maintenance and field modifications.
- Ordering and managing repair parts cycle times
- Maintaining daily communications with customers to ensure resolution and proper follow-up

Production Supervisor KHS Machinery Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

JUN 2010 to DEC 2012

- Delivery of quality production engineering solutions in response to operational and manufacturing needs
- Handling Manufacturing department; Planning and execution of assembly and testing and dispatch of Machines, Change Parts & Spare assemblies

Education

Diploma Mechanical Engineer – 2007 to 2010, From R.C.Technical Institute(Technical Education Board), Ahmedabad with 60%.

Declaration

I hereby do solemnly affirm that the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge.